Guide to the George Coffin papers, 1858-1896 MS2048
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Coffin papers
1858-1896
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Coffin, George Yost
MS2048
7.5 Linear Feet
Collection includes original political cartoons from Washington newspapers; lithographic reproductions of other political cartoons; original pen and ink illustrations of civil war stories; scrapbooks containing original political cartoons, lithographic reproductions of cartoons, original sketches, and newspaper clippings; diaries; and loose sketches and photographs. These materials date from 1858-1896.
Box UP0001
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Biographical Note
George Yost Coffin (1850-1896) was a prominent Washington D.C. political cartoonist of the late nineteenth century. Coffin came to Washington with his parents in 1858. During the civil war years he was a student at Columbian College (later George Washington University). Following his graduation in 1869 he attended the Columbian University Law School, completing his degree in 1871. In 1872 Coffin found employment as a clerk in the Revenue Marine division of the U.S. Department of the Treasury, a post which he held until his death in 1896. His career as a political cartoonist started in the mid-1870s with the first illustrated paper in Washington, D.C., the Illustrated Washington Chronicle. After its demise, Coffin contributed freely to a number of journals of politics and humor including Harper's Weekly, Puck, and The Judge, until the Washington weekly, The Hatchet, was started in 1883 and engaged Coffin as its cartoonist. While his tenure there was short-lived, The Hatchet having soon discontinued its pictorial feature, Coffin's artistic stock was on the rise. By the mid-1880s he was contributing cartoons to practically every local paper that printed pictures. At one time Coffin was drawing for The Washington Star, The Critic, The Sunday Herald, The National Republican, The Washington Post, and The National Tribune, as well as for some New York papers representing every shade of political, opinion. In 1891, however, Coffin gave up his free lance work when he became the official cartoonist of The Washington Post. This position he held until his death in 1896 at the age of 46.
Collection Scope and Content
Material in this collection include original political cartoons from Washington newspapers; lithographic reproductions of other political cartoons; original pen and ink illustrations of civil war stories; scrapbooks containing original political cartoons, lithographic reproductions of cartoons, original sketches, and newspaper clippings; diaries; and loose sketches and photographs. These materials date from 1858-1896.
The largest group of materials are the 352 large-size, original political cartoons, 193 of which were published in "The Washington Post" during his tenure as political cartoonist (1891-1896) All but 25 of these have been identified by date and caption. Other publications to which Coffin contributed and which are represented in this collection are "The Washington Hatchet," "The Critic," "The National Tribune," and "The Washington Daily News." These cartoons are not dated or captioned for the most part. Another segment of the collection consists of 61 sets of civil war story illustrations made by Coffin which appeared in separately published personal accounts of the war and in various Washington periodicals in the two decades which followed the American Civil War. The Coffin papers also contain six scrapbooks of original sketches (1858-1869), newspaper clippings of articles illustrated by Coffin (1875-1885), original political cartoons (1880s), lithographic reproductions of cartoons (1890s), and articles published about Coffin after his death. Finally, the collection includes four volumes of Coffin's handwritten diaries (1859-1868), covering the period of his undergraduate years at Columbian College.
The George Y. Coffin papers were the gift of Ms. Isabelle Solomons in June, 1926.
Collection Organization
Organized into five series: Series 1. Political cartoons, 1891-1896; Series 2. Civil War illustrations, 1860s - 1890s; Series 3. Scrapbooks, 1858-1890s; Series 4. Diaries, 1859-1861; and Series 5. Miscellaneous Loose Sketches and Photographs, undated.
Collection note
Please note: there is a paper finding aid available in the reading room that has details for the political cartoons including titles, dates, and sizes. Please see staff for assistance.
Diaries; Scrapbooks; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865; Autobiography; Political satire; Washington (D.C.); Photographs; Newspapers; Cartoonists; Coffin, George Yost; Columbian College in the District of Columbia; George Washington University--History
- Political Cartoons, 1891-1896, undated; MS2048 Series 1
  - Scene at the Gridiron Club Banquet Table, 02/08/1891 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Officers of the Club, 02/08/1891 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A Peripatetic Plenipotentiary, 05/03/1891 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Death in the Mail Car, 05/17/1891 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Home Again - A Warm Welcome From Dame Columbia and Good Citizens and Candidates, 05/17/1891 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - None Too Soon, 06/07/1891 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Lord High Executioner, 06/28/1891 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Fourth at the District Buildings, 07/04/1891 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Trying the Rain Balloons, 07/05/1891 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Justice Cutting the Wire, 07/12/1891 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - On to Washington, 08/09/1891 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Vacant Seat, 09/06/1891 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Home Again - From Foreign (New Jersey) Shores, 09/16/1891 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - A Vision of Two Sisters A.D. 1891, 09/27/1891 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - A Gem of Official Literature, 10/18/1891 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Grand Inter-Urban High Kicking Match for the Next Republican Convention, 11/22/1891 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Uncle Sam's Thanksgiving Dinner A.D. 1891, 11/26/1891 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Same Old Circus, 12/06/1891 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Wanted - A Leader for Washington's Four Hundred, 12/13/1891 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Old Tempus Fugit, 01/03/1892 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Dogs of War, 01/06/1892 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - To Arlington, 01/10/1892 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - An Early Start, 01/17/1892 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Leap Year A.D. 1892, 02/28/1892 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The British Tweed, 03/13/1892 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Modern Pilgrim's Progress, 03/20/1892 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - An Obdurate Deity, 04/24/1892 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - May Day 1892, 05/01/1892 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: Hard Luck, 06/25/1893 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: The Day We Consecrate, 06/25/1893 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: Pedestrian Pleasures of Washington, 06/25/1893 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: Up or Down?, 06/25/1893 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: A Terrible Warning, 06/11/1893 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: Perseus and Andromeda, 06/11/1893 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: A Mourning Queen, 06/11/1893 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: The Real Issue, 06/18/1893 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: An Embarrassment of Riches, 06/18/1893 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: Sympathy that Counts, 06/18/1893 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - The Post's Panorama of the Week: A Gory Governor, 07/16/1893 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - With the Compliments of the Post to Congress: T.B.R, "Well, Boys, What are you Going to Do About it?", 08/06/1893 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - A Run on the Bank, 08/13/1893 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - The Congressman's Mid-Summer Night's Dream, 08/13/1893 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - The Wanderers' Return, 08/13/1893 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - The Post's Panorama of Recent Events: Three of a Kind, 08/13/1893 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - The Post's Panorama of Recent Events: The Militiaman and the Mermaid, 08/13/1893 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - The Post's Pictorial View of Passing Events: Other Distinguished Arrivals, 09/03/1893 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - The Post's Pictorial View of Passing Events: A Case of Suspended Suspensions, 09/03/1893 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - The Post's Pictorial Commentary on Things Current and to Come, 11/26/1893 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - A Sevendays Summary in Black and White, 09/23/1894 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - The Post's Pictorial Pops at Things Past, Present, and to Come, 09/30/1894 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - A Fall Back - More Brutality on the Football Field, 12/08/1894 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - At the Theatre and Concert, 12/12/1894 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Sprung by Springer, 12/18/1894 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - A Merry Christmas to the Patrons of the Post, 12/25/1894 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Wishing You a Happier New Year, 01/01/1895 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - A Spasm of Morality, 01/13/1895 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Where will this Air Ship Light?, 01/14/1895 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Majesty of the Law, 01/21/1895 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - And the Cat Came Back!, 01/23/1895 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Men Who Fought. The Men Who Talk., 01/26/1895 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Last of the Seals, 02/02/1895 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Democratic Shadow, 02/06/1895 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - In Nick of Time, 02/09/1895 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Under Charity's Protecting Wing, 02/10/1895 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - David's New Toy, 02/19/1895 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Design for Grand Mortuary ument for the New Capitol Terrace, 02/20/1895 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - What! Ho! For Mexico!, 02/21/1895 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - High Carnival on Capitol Hill, 02/26/1895 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Turn About is Fair Play, 03/03/1895 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Are We Becoming a Nation of Thieves?, 03/10/1895 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Eclipse of North Carolina, 03/12/1895 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Under the New Law, 03/14/1895 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Our Inhospitable Hospitals, 03/20/1895 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Tarrible Times in ole Vaginny, 03/23/1895 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Mysterious Three, 03/31/1895 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Praise from Sir Hubert, 04/07/1895 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Weighed in the Balance, 04/08/1895 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - A Story Without Words, 04/26/1895 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Higher than Gilderoy's Kite, 04/27/1895 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - A Sweeping Charge, 04/28/1895 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Passing it Along, 04/30/1895 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Potatoe - Culture in High Places, 05/05/1895 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - An Apotheosis in Trousers, 05/09/1895 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The Eyes of Delaware are on Them, 05/11/1895 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - The Little Pilgrim, 05/15/1895 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Right Hand of Citizenship, 05/17/1895 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - The Coming Woman, 05/26/1895 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Gresham, 05/29/1895 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Thirty Years After, 05/30/1895 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Some Unseasonable Swelterings, 06/02/1895 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - A Ten-Day's Wonder, 06/08/1895 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The New Atlanta, 06/12/1895 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Off For Camp, 06/13/1895 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Mr. Brice Has Gone to Ohio on Important Railroad Business, 06/15/1895 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Reform Run Mad, 06/16/1895 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - A Week in June, 06/23/1895 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - In the Search-light of Truth, 06/27/1895 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - The Day We Celebrate, 07/04/1895 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Midsummer Athletics A.D. 1895, 07/07/1895 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - The Unanimous Sentiment, 07/09/1895 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Again the Eagle Bird Wins, 07/10/1895 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mr. Pfeffer's New Party, 07/21/1895 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - The Sea Serpent and the Lighthouse Keeper, 07/24/1895 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Here We Are Again, 07/31/1895 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - A "Hill" Horse with a Pull, 08/08/1895 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - A High-Roller Comptroller, 08/09/1895 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - It is the Caws, 08/15/1895 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - An Old Saw Reset, 08/16/1895 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Oh, for a lodge in some vast wilderness, some boundless continguity of shade, 08/18/1895 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Under the Shadow of Bunker Hill, 08/29/1895 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - A Tale of Two Cities, 09/04/1895 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - For the Cup, 09/08/1895 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Seagirt 1895, 09/10/1895 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - I don't want to Play in your Yard, 09/15/1895 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Miles Standish's Courtship, 09/23/1895 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - A National Calamity, 10/29/1895 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Political Services of Matthew Stanley Quay, 11/17/1895 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Honor to Whom Honor is Due, 11/21/1895 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - They Give Thanks A.D. 1895, 11/28/1895 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - The Secretary and the Hayseed, 12/15/1895 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Glad You Agree with Us, Mr. President, 12/19/1895 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - If John Came to the Senate, 12/21/1895 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - The National Credit, 12/24/1895 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - With ey to Burn, 12/29/1895 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Leap Year 1896, 01/01/1896 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - The Same Old Senate, 01/11/1896 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Honors are Easy, 01/18/1896 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Engaged B. Harrison, 01/19/1896 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - An Undaunted Crusader, 01/23/1896 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Two Patriotic Sons of the District, 01/29/1896 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Columbia's Leap Year Valentine, 02/14/1896 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Post No Bills, 02/16/1896 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - None Too Soon, 02/29/1896 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Hoop! La! There They Go. "On a Bicycle Built for Six.", 03/13/1896 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - The Post Gallery - no. 13 - The Two Augurs, 03/15/1896 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - The Wizard of the Nile, 03/22/1896 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Something Wrong, 04/04/1896 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Honors are Easy. End of the Great Wind-Jamming Contest Way Down in Jaw-Jaw, 04/15/1896 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - A Finger in Every Pie, 04/23/1896 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - May Day 1896, 05/01/1896 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - One More Unfortunate, 05/03/1896 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - That's Right, Mr. President; Give 'Em Fitz, 05/20/1896 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - The Swan Song of the Boss, 05/23/1896 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - To the Heroic Dead, 05/30/1896 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - The McKinley Cyclone, 06/01/1896 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - That Game of "eze Out" in the Senate, 06/06/1896 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - "For the Major", 06/07/1896 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Fourth of July Patriotism (limited), 06/27/1896 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - The Founder's Dream, 07/11/1896 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Onward, Christian Soldiers", 07/13/1896 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Saved From the Flood. The Post's Gallery of Modern Masterpieces - no. 17, 07/19/1896 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - A Harmless Explosion, 07/26/1896 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Will Hoke Fly?, 08/02/1896 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Oh, say! Is young Lochinvar come out of the west?, 08/09/1896 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - His Platform, 08/11/1896 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Again the Lady and the Tiger, 08/14/1896 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Ye merry birds", 08/27/1896 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Welcome, Li Hung Chiang, 08/28/1896 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Oh! Wert thou in the cauld, cau'd blast", 09/05/1896 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The unhappy candidate: A reminiscence of capitol park, 09/22/1896 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - The country is safe, 09/25/1896 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Alarming Nightmare of the Hon. J. Sterling Morton, 10/16/1896 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Ye merrie joust of arms, 10/18/1896 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - In the Balance, 11/03/1896 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The of Austerlitz, 11/04/1896 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "Shake! Billy Bryan!", 11/04/1896 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "Is it all over?", 11/06/1896 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Peace Prosperity Plenty, 11/08/1896 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - "Come on, boys; Let's arbitrate", 11/12/1896 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Baltztey Brothers, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Urduray, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Parks, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Hay, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - M. M. Parker, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Boguton, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Robert, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - B.H. Warner, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - (no title), undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - A Group of Guests, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Dame Columbia, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - The Tiger and the Candidate, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Cleveland and the Public Credit, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Election Returns at the Post, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - A High-Handed Outrage, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Marching Band, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Abdication of Queen Lil, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - An Ill-Starred Structure, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Welcome Endeavorers, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - In Senate and House, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Hail the Coming, Speed the Parting Guest, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - The Arms of Virginia, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - When the Smoke of Battle has Cleared Away, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - The Post's Sketch-Book of the Week, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Love and Laughter, 11/19/1885 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Government Printing Office, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cleveland and the Issues, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Thanksgiving 1885, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dead at the Post of Duty, 01/29/1891 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - David Crockett and the Coon, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - A Case of Unstable Equilibrium, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Mail for Gov. Hill, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Investigating the Silver Pool, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Known by his Chips, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Soldiers Orphans, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Emptying the Reservoir, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - (no title), undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Free Trade and Tin Plates, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Attacking Justice for the Veteran, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Rout of Rodes, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Recollections of Sherman, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Pap Thomas to the Rescue, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Ringing a Bell, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Leaving for War, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Fire, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Charge, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Extract from Gen. Wainwright's Report, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Pension Lie, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Street vs. Sidewalk, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - The Statue of Liberty, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Military Parade, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Advancing Women's Organizations, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Uncle Sam to Congress, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Winning with Hands Down, 10/18/1884 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - X-mas '84, 1884 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - The District Commission, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Explosion, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Leaving Cleveland in the Dust, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Baltimore or Bust, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - W. & G. R.R., undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Excelsior, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - An Official Inspecting Tour, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Spending the Surplus, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Arresting a Boy, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - District Commission, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Women Running the Country, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - The Spectre of the Aqueduct, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - A Record that does not Record, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - The Washington Hotel Keeper's Dream, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Reform at U.S. Treasury, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - The Political Millennium, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - A New Era, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - The Rifles' Fair 1885 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Cape May, NJ, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Inauguration Day 1889 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - An Entirely Amicable and Harious Contest, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Easter Egg Rolling, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - The Aesthete, the Boss, and the Widow, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - In the Dark and Bloody Ground, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - The Free Trade Phonograph, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Walpurgis Night, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Uncle Sam's Tavern, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - How it is Done!, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - The Veteran, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - In a Congenial Role and yet He is not Happy, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - A Tub to the Whale, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Easy Winners, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - A Cold Day, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - (no title), undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - A Good-Natured Giant, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Remembering Lincoln, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The G.O.P Indulges in a Gigantic Jag of Joy!, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - The Judgment of Paris, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - A Long Range Enthusiast, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Manhattan Day at the Fair, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Congratulations! Mr. President, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Eager for the Fray, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Saved from the Deep, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Stabbed in the House of His ends, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 10th Annual Dinner of the Gridiron Club, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Moving the Capitol, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Our National Disgrace, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - The Canal Boy of Ohio, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - (no title), undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Which Pill Will He Take, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - (no title), undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - (no title), undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - (no title), undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - A Military Execution, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - The White Elephant, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - (no title), undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Exit Brewster, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - A Quintette Worth Many Millions, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Columbus Discovering (South) America From the East Front of the Capitol, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Neck and Neck, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - (Title illegible), undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - (Title illegible), undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Puck's Bad Boy, 06/28/1884 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Over the Garden Wall, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Post and McPherson, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - How He Has Put his Foot In It, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - No Paralysis Here, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Another of Cleveland's Vices, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Ye Spanish Don/Ye American Farmer, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Not So Heavy as it Looks, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - A Diplomatic Episode, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Consulting the Oracle, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Around the Week in Washington, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - The Nation's Vampire, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Presented At Court, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - At the Tomb of Grant, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - The Chicago Grab-Bag, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Taking His Medicine, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - (no title), undated (Box 7, Folder 40)